

# TAYLOR JOHNSON

SR. CONTENT CURATOR & FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

213-440-8966

♠ Los Angeles, CA

in tajohnsonn

tajohnsonn

# EDUCATION

# **BACHELOR'S DEGREE**

California State University, Monterey Bay 2016

# **Full Stack Coding Bootcamp**

UCLA Extension, Remote 2019-PRESENT

#### SKILLS

# | Professional

Adobe Photoshop

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap Framework

Figma

Responsive Design

Node.js

Javascript

Git

# SUMMARY

I am a marketing professional with growing skills in front-end web development. I am a current student at UCLA Extension attending a full stack web development course. I have created projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and making AJAX calls. My passion is to create a clean user friendly experience for all.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# SR. CONTENT CURATOR

Shopkick, REMOTE / 2018-Present

Shopkick is the fun and easy way to earn free gift cards for everyday shopping. Millions of people use Shopkick every day to discover new products, plan shopping trips and earn rewards online, in their app, and in stores everywhere.

- Manage mobile shopping app's full content pipeline from origination, execution, QA to release
- Create HTML code for marketing emails
- Created and manage editorial calendars for the team influenced by market trends, engagement metrics, and client requests.
- Create mocks for lookbooks using InDesign, and Photoshop.

# LEAD INSTAGRAM SPAM ANALYST

Facebook (Contract), Menlo Park, CA / 2017-2018

- Evaluate 2,000+ Instagram accounts daily for spam and abuse with >99% accuracy
- Answer many different inquiries through the online queue and create process improvements within queue
- Identify trends in spam behavior and derive actionable insights to improve team strategy and policy enforcement.

# CONTENT REVIEW SPECIALIST

Google (Contract), San Jose, CA / 2016-2017

- Review 1000+ articles per week by more than 300 publishers to observe and report error trends to project manager for resolution.
- Suggest and implement process improvements.
- Demonstrate critical thinking and attention to detail to review content against existing policies.